Charles Schuchert Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Manuscript material, 1904-1942; Series V
  - Plates. Hand-colored maps used to create the plates in "Paleogeography of North America."., 002481
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002664
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002665
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002666
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002667
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002668
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002669
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002670
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002671
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002672
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002673
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002674
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002675
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002676
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002677
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002678
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002679
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002680
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002681
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002682
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002683
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002684